Hello
guys. Good morning. Welcome, welcome,
welcome
to another episode of S Talk Show. Hi.
We're going to have a drink. Okay. So, I
discovered rum.
So, can you see? So, this is rum cheap.
I discovered I think this is my favorite
booze now. Okay. So, I don't like red
wine. I don't like beer because beer is
bitter
and red wine is also like bitter, like
weird taste.
And white wine is like sour kind of odd.
I don't like them. And I discovered that
when you drink red wine, you have this
handover. Okay. But I discovered I think
I like vodka. Vodka. And now rum. Okay.
The rum is fantastic. And you got this
this big giant bottle like 1.7 liter
from from Costco. Okay. I think this is
fantastic. So today, what are we going
to talk about? I don't know. Um I feel
like, you know, it's been five days I
haven't done live stream. So I feel like
do some random chat. Okay. And have a
drink. Then [snorts] I'm going to have
dinner in in in like 20 minutes. We'll
see. Okay. [snorts] So, random chat
and drink and random chat.
Okay. So, let me show you my screen. So,
by the way, this is ultimate hacking
keyboard. I have a review on my website
all over. And uh let me mention again.
So, I got this um
this this amazing thing. Okay, this is
SWAL board. SV A L S S V A L B O A R D.
Okay, the guy is fantastic. So, search
the web SV A L B O A R D. And also I
kind of have a short preview of that. I
haven't I just never got used, you know,
I never practiced. So, well, the reason
I haven't practiced is because kind of
my life issues. Okay. It's just my
personal life issues. I I need to get
things going. So, I just never, you
know, like put time to do that. Anyway,
so that's a that's a issue. So, what am
I doing? So, let's begin to get drunk.
Okay. So, let me show you my screen.
Okay. And stop this YouTube. Stop.
Okay. We got uh So, if you are here, say
hi. Love to see your comments. Okay. So
let's uh so this pop out this window.
Um and so let's uh Okay. So today's
topic is just random. Okay. I just feel
like talking about some random [ __ ]
Emacs. Okay.
So um yeah. So let me tell you guys what
we going to tell you guys. Uh well, I'm
going to tell you guys some of the um uh
interesting things I've done. Of course,
programming. I've been so busy coding.
So busy with the AI menace today, you
know, and I've been just coding and
coding and and posting huge amount of
Twitter.
Uh and for some reason, you know, the
deep state is promoting me on Twitter
[laughter] a little bit. Okay. like for
the past 10 years like whatever whatever
I post like nobody read it I mean
because I anyway for for anyway
anyway that's that's another thing okay
so anyway on my Twitter so anyway so
I've been posting a lot on Twitter but
let me tell you about what I have been
coding okay I've been so extremely busy
coding in fact that's that that's the
case for the past um 10 years to but
anyway so so um so anyway so yeah so let
me start to show you okay so mostly okay
I forgot I need to put this here mostly
on JavaScript and CSS and stuff okay so
you go to my website
cheers can you see me uh yes you can
okay
so kasali.info info.info.
Fantastic. Okay. So, you go to I have
like one, two, three, uh, one, you know,
one, two, three, four, five, six blog
here plus another five on.org.
Okay. Uh, so anyway, so you go to my web
dev blog. So, I've been extremely busy
here. So, I created week map finally
after 10 years. I finally wrote a
tutorial on the JavaScript weak map.
Cheers. If you're here, say hi. Okay.
Hello, Coin.
Coin says, "So after 20 years, I'm
moving to Emacs." [laughter]
That's [snorts] fantastic. It's kind of
late, isn't it? Because I've been
wondering, you know, AI is kind of
killing Emacs.
Why is that? Because AI
because AI, you know, with AI, you code
less. A lot of people code less. Wait,
is my microphone like getting red? Um,
so let me turn it down a little bit. I
don't want my microphone getting red.
Okay,
so AI is um wait so let me adjust adjust
adjust adjust. Okay. So, it's possible
that AI is killing Emacs because with AI
people code less. They don't need to
like like code so much. Therefore,
you know, therefore they use Emac list
because Emacs is known as these powerful
uh elaborate text editor because you
can, for example, you can see all my
directories. I can copy files, you know,
rename files and everything you've seen
I've done, you know. So it's like a
system, but now with AI, you don't code
so much. So you don't need that system
anymore. Kind of like that. So that's um
it's just my guess. Okay, we don't know.
Like nobody know what's going on. But
the other thing is that there is this
guy. I don't remember if I told the
story before on my live stream.
Where's my drink? Okay, [laughter] I'm
gonna get drunk today. Okay, so you can
see me drunk. So, so there is this guy
extreme emac this expert one of the top
one Emacs and Emac this coder I respect
so there's this guy so his name is um
you know his name is um Christopher
something you know he goes by new he
goes by the handle new so let's search
for it n u l not found. Uh, C H R I S.
Wait. So, you go to my Emacs blog. So,
scroll up down so you can see my Emacs
blog and Christopher. So, search for
Christopher. Why can't I find it? Search
for No.
Uh, why can't I find it? What? What?
I was pretty sure I'm pretty sure I
blogged about him because
you know did I talk ever talk about him
anyway? So I'm pretty sure I blogged.
Okay, so maybe it's not on my Emacs
blog. Then let's go to my programming
programmer programming blog my multiple
so many blocks. So search for new.
Okay, you don't want that. No. Search
for C H R I S.
What? Not found. Now I'm pissed. Now I'm
destined. Destined to find it.
Okay. Hello guys. I'll answer your
questions. Okay. Hold on a second. So go
to e uh
undo. Go to Emac blog. Okay. Search for
wait list matching lines. N U L L. No
list matching lines. N U L. Maybe
there's one single L only. No list
matching lines. [clears throat] S C H R
I S. No. [ __ ] I'm pissed. Now go to
my programming blog. Showing browser.
Okay. Go to Emacs.
Search for Chris. No. Search for uh no
there. Wait. Wait. That's type. No. No.
What the [ __ ] I I'm I'm 100% sure I
blogged about it. Okay.
So, why does that not happen? I don't
know. So, let me um Okay. Now, more
drink.
Run. Rum. Did you know that rum is made
of sugar can? Amazing. Okay. Like while
I'm drinking, I ask AI questions. I ask
AI questions all the time.
AI told me like AI like what are the
interesting stories about alcohol like
rum their history like tell me something
interesting he you know and vodka and
and China baiu and Mexicans tequila you
know
Mexicans tequila are made of uh this
this kind of sugar plant okay called
acqu or something very you know kind of
interesting. So anyway rum is made of
sugar can and rum is the um what Brit
British sailors drink because back then
you know like imagine 100 years ago or
200 years ago they have to sail across
the ocean. You know the Brit the British
United Kingdom are known for their you
know their navy. They [ __ ] around the
world. The white men the Brit white men.
Okay. So but they you know you you you
you uh you you you sell on the ocean if
you keep the water the water goes to
rot. Okay. The the water is going to be
rotted be rotten. It's going to grow
mold. So but they discovered if you you
know rum is easy to keep it healthy you
know so so the British sellers has Rome
as ration okay so now I'm a British
seller
[laughter]
so what what are you guys saying so
after 20 years I'm moving to Emacs I
think with AI
uh I think with AI people break more can
trust new developers us with Vim uh and
Vim.
Uh yeah, you know, we don't know what's
going on going to go on with AI and and
all those uh the vibe coders, they are
kind of idiots. Okay. [snorts] Emacs is
my favorite software ever written.
Fantastic commentary actually. I think
that's true for me too. Is is Emacs my
favorite? Uh I think kind of. Okay. or
one of
um because I used to say you know I used
to say that the most
if you can pick one software that
represent the technology of humanity of
the entire human history history
[snorts] I used to say like 10 years ago
that would be Google Earth okay
uh Google Earth I don't know if you zuma
young people know about it but but
Google Earth was a software that shows
the earth rotating and today like since
about 10 years ago now they have a web
uh they have a web version so let me
just show you okay Google earth it's
kind of like Google map in fact today
there's not much difference okay but
basically it allows you to see any place
in the world the earth okay Google earth
so in my opinion I used to say if you
can show pick one software to
demonstrate um the technology
technological advancement the level of
of humanity that would be Google Earth
because Google Earth represents the
entire computer
um technology. Okay, like the entire the
data structure, the science of data
structure, the science of algorithms,
the science of networking, the science
of uh operating systems actually not not
so much of that.
Okay. Networking, satellite technology,
uh communication technology, signal
processing,
you know that that you know and and and
also computer graphics. Okay. So this so
if you can have only one software to
represent the level of advancement of
human society
Google Earth is one great representation
okay in my opinion you know like imagine
like anywhere on earth you can you can
you can look at you know you can zoom
down you know so let's see uh Shanghai
okay so you know I never been to China
so let's see Um, by the way, Google, you
know, uh, you know, China because
there's political political issues with
USA. So, they don't allow Google to, uh,
have lots of photos and stuff, but let
anyway. So, let's go to let's see what
what they show on Shanghai. Okay. So,
you there it is. You zoom in
Shanghai. So, you you know there it is
Shanghai. Can so can you see like the
the big um
skyscrapers? Uh there there are some
amazing quite clear. Can you see? Quite
amazing. You see? Uh but they don't have
Oh, wait. They they do have street view.
Uh us not so much because they, you
know, China doesn't allow Google like
nosing around.
Uh but you do have uh some of it. Okay.
Amazing. Actually, I haven't seen this,
you know. So, so there it is. Oh, okay.
So, you can see some of it here. So,
let's do
street view. Okay.
There it is. Shanghai street view.
Amazing. Can you see?
Wow. Wow. So, so um
wait,
why is my keyboard um
Okay, so you have to Anyway, one more
drink. Um
hold on a second. Okay, I need to um
There's no more drink.
So that's what I'm saying. You know, if
we can pick one software to represent
humanity's technology,
I would say Google Earth.
Now, if you can pick another that would
be some some some 3D game. Okay? Because
gaming technology is truly the
uh conglomeration the summary of all
computer science technology. Okay? So,
now second shot. Drum.
Oh my god, I'm going to get drunk today.
[laughter]
Why not?
[clears throat]
I type so much, you know. I type so
much. I have hand pen and it's killing
me. Killing me. But I'm still struggling
uh in making it.
So anyway, so so you can see so so here
is Shanghai. So let's see. Other images
are not available here. Try different
locations to find street view historical
images. Shut the [ __ ] up. Okay. So
anyway, here is Shanghai.
So can So what can we see here? Okay, so
for some reason this kind of always
stuck.
Uh wait. Uh okay. So what?
Oh [ __ ]
Okay. We exit by mistake. But you know
anyway that's uh Google Earth. Okay. So
they came to the web. Now there's a web
version but before you like 20 uh 15
years ago or when did it begin? About
2010 or before. Okay. So you have to
download the app Google Earth. But now
it's available on the web because
JavaScript because JavaScript ECMAS
script 2015 and so many happenings.
Okay. So Google Earth. Okay. That's
Google Earth. That's kind of represents
the entire
uh computer science networking computer
graphics algorithms and database massive
database because you know you need to
know all the you know you retrieve all
the geol locations right. So that that's
kind of you know that's what I say.
So but Emacs uh not really. So you know
so Emacs used to be the most complex
software I would say like 20 years ago
or 30 years ago in the 1980s 1990s even.
It's like extremely supreme eag but not
today. Today is like it's really kind of
nothing. Okay.
Uh, so, okay. So, let's see your
comments. Okay. And I wanted to tell you
about my webdev. Okay. So, I've been
massively coding. Oh, okay. So, hold on
a second. So, let's get back to the
Christopher Wellins. I need to mention
that guy. Okay. So, hold on a second.
Okay. Go to Emacs blog. Search for uh
quiz. Okay. The reason I didn't find it
because I probably logged it off because
now it's um
you see Yeah. So I lo I I I moved it
into archive. So the my last post on my
um Emacs blog is is July because I post
so many you know. So, so the for the
June month of June, May, April and so
on, I moved them into archive. So, you
go to the archive here. Now, you search
for Christopher.
What?
[sighs and gasps]
What? Uh, Chris. Okay. What?
S E Emacs blog archive. Okay. 2025
January January to June. So search for
CHIS is not found. What the [ __ ] is
that? I don't understand. Hold on a
second. Okay. So let me do that in
Emacs. Search for CHIS not found. Search
for no not found. Okay. So now let's do
that again for uh uh for the kasar
programming blog that there okay
so go to emac
bookmark open the programming blog go to
the top search for archive okay open the
archive page showing browser okay now go
to the 2026 archive 2026 January up to
um up to April. Okay. Now, search for
Chris. Search for new.
Not that one. That's type new. That's uh
that's JavaScript. Okay. Search for
Christopher.
Uh Christopher Starchy. No, that's a
different guy. What the [ __ ] Um
okay so so what I'm saying is that so
there is some issue
so I might have instead of blogging
about Christopher wellins I must have
done a talk show about him so let's
search search it talk show talk show
Okay. Excell 2024. Which is best dispac
closure wam language. That's episode
255. That's kind of old. Okay. Search
again. Milk tits carrier tits emac this
command to change title case. That's
episode 799
uh a month ago. Okay. Uh search again.
talk show 798. Write JavaScript to
create cascading style sheet sheet oak
LCH colors. Okay, search again. Uh,
okay. So, let me find it. Um,
okay.
Okay. Let's have another drink.
What the [ __ ] The Christopher Wellins,
where where are you?
Okay. So, I'm now determined to find
find about it. Okay. So, let's go to
talk show. Okay. Because I can find it
for sure. So, here is my talk show page
on.info.
All my past talk shows are logged here.
So all I have to do is search for
Christopher Wellins. Okay. So uh first
of all you can search for his blog Chris
Wellins. Okay. No new he goes by the
name. So there it is. No new program.
That's a guy. Okay. He is the let me
just tell you about him. So he is the
number one emac this and Emacs coder. I
respect
number one basically. Okay. He is a top
expert of C or C++ I forgot which and
he's a top expert of EMACP. Okay. So he
knows computer science but he's not my
type. Okay. He's like more like the bit
diddler type of guy. He's into C and C++
and he I uh and and he knows emacisp you
know he's expert but however he's a type
of guy uh what I would call uh bit
diddlers okay so typically this type of
people are like C and C++ expert they
view computation from from from the
point of view of of the hardware okay so
They bit us, okay? They they did little
bits. They talk about references,
pointer, you know, that kind of thing.
That's the way they think, okay?
As opposed to on the other hand the
mathematical mathematician type of guy
or theoretical computer science type of
guy who thinks in terms of lambda
calculus or combinators or type theory
you know or the functions mathematical
functions you know so so that's a
totally opposite
kind of people uh which original lispers
are kind of like that original lispers
from 1960s, 1970s, 1980s. Okay. Okay.
So, the the guy Chris Wellins is not
that. He's more of the bit did like C
C++ like memory reference that type of
guy. Okay. However, I respect him highly
because he's really expert.
So, he wrote a few articles. I I I don't
remember I talked about it but he wrote
a few articles so he explored into AI so
much so that and he found out that he's
now completely an AI coder he stopped
coding at all he doesn't code anymore he
just use AI completely
you know but but he's he he he he's not
the Zoomer idiot like who don't know
what they doing he's a true expert
But you know by his judgment he started
to use AI completely. So that's amazing.
So and he also have a Emacs. You see I
have officially retired from Emacs. So
he doesn't use Emacs anymore. He was you
know he was the the top most EMAC expert
producing so many the greatest Emacs uh
packages such as Alfeed but he stopped.
Amazing. You know, and he's don't he
don't he stopped using Emacs because
there's no need anymore. Amazing.
So, there it is. That's his story. Okay.
Christopher Wellins. Okay.
Cheers.
I'm I'm I'm right now um
20% drunk. I'm still pretty sane
at this moment. Anyway, check check him
out. Okay, now I don't remember. So,
where did I mention him in S talk show?
So, I I must um I must find it now. So,
search
no. Just search for new. Okay.
So, uh no type. No, we don't want no
type. We are talking about um this
enlarge the window. So, are you guys
still with me?
If you have comments, questions, post
it. Okay, I'll get it to the new
program. Okay.
Uh, no JavaS. So, we got I got a lot
links to JavaScript. No, no, that's not
we want. Okay. Close it. Search for
Let's just search for his blog. Okay.
New program. So his blog is named
newprogram. Okay. Search for it.
Newprogram.com.
Okay. Search in my talk show. I'll find
it. There it is. So 2023 December I
talked about him. There's only one
instance. What the [ __ ]
No. Okay. So,
so in 2023 December 1st, I talked about
Chris Christopher
Wellins or was it just Chris Wellan?
What's his what's his name? Chris
Wellins. Okay.
So, uh, so that's kind of strange
because I was pretty sure I talked about
him this year.
Uh, maybe I didn't. Uh, okay. So I'm now
30% drunk. So
So the question is, did I did I talk
about Christopher Wellen
this year 2026?
I think I I pretty sure I did e either
blogged him about him or
uh live streamed about him. But now I
cannot find it. That's kind of odd.
Okay.
So, let me make some one more effort.
So, go to my Emacs blog. Showing
browser. Now, search for uh wait, search
for uh new program not doesn't exist.
Now, go to archive page. Okay. Showing
browser. Now, um go to
2025 archive.
Search for it. doesn't exist.
Okay. So, uh [groaning]
Okay. So, maybe I didn't talk about him
that much.
That's odd. 2025.
So, okay. So, my Emacs
my Emacs blog is getting too long. I
need to archive part of it.
Okay. Because right now this page is too
long.
So but I cannot find any mention of new
program his website. So that's
interesting. That means I actually did
not mention him this year.
Okay. So now let's go to my programming
blog showing browser. Now did I mention
him there? New program. No. Okay.
So let's go to the bottom. Uh okay. So
the last one is May. So let's go to the
archive.
My programming blog archive. Let's go to
January. Okay. Open it. Now did I
mention him? No. Okay. So now I have
made sure
I have verified that I did not mention
Christopher Wellen the guy in my blogs.
That's odd. So I must remembered it
wrong. [snorts]
Uh okay. Anyway, so anyway, I'm telling
you guys, okay, so I recommend check out
his blog because he he he went into AI
in depth. you know, he started to use
the AI agent, uh, the AI coding agent,
and he completely switched to AI. Okay,
so that's amazing. And this is a guy I
highly respect and trust. Okay, not the
Zuma vibe called idiots.
Okay, I think I'm going to have one more
shot, one more shot of this. Okay, then
that's it for today. Maybe 10 more
minutes. Okay.
Uh, and I haven't talked about um what
I've done on my web blog, so I will do
so now. Okay.
Now, after this shot, I will be 60%
drunk.
I'm I'm still sabber.
Well, I'm I'm well not 100% sabber, but
I'm still sin. Okay, at this point. Now,
let's see the comments.
Am I So, how many people are watching? I
suppose, yeah, eight people. So, when
you get drunk, you get more people
watches. Idiot.
Uh, cheers. So I hope you guys have a
good time
during this time. The AI minus
as far as it you know from my
perspective is AI minutes. It made me
depressed.
So I'm destined to find it. Okay. Do you
watch the World Cup? No. Okay. So that's
about football. So today you know soccer
American would call it soccer the but
the rest of world would call it
football.
You know you basically a game you play
with your feet but not the American
idiots. American idiots got this Rambo
this eggshaped Rambo. Okay, that's
that's you know that's an American um
word football but in the rest of the
world it means what American call soccer
is a amazing sport I I love it you know
when I was younger I I kind of watch it
all the time I don't play myself but
because my f my my dad is so much into
it because it's amazing you know so I
you know anyway so I find this game
my opinion of this game is actually it's
a it's a great game it's amazing so you
play with your feet
okay what American would call soccer but
the rest of the world English speaking
words call it football okay foot you
play with your foot so it's amazing but
but but but today I'm getting too old.
Okay. So, I didn't watch it. I don't
even know who is winning. I think I
think the the last um competition is
like England versus Argentina, something
like that. I don't know. Yeah. So, I
haven't been following it
because I'm getting old. Okay. I'm
getting old and sad.
Um, so no, I haven't been uh following
it. World Cup. Cheers.
So, next comment. I'll check out No's
post. Even if we don't write code
by hand, I think it's great to know
these tools. I like tools that last.
Okay. Cheers.
>> [sighs]
>> Ah,
you know, today I just felt like I need
to do some uh live stream. It's kind of
sad because for many reasons,
[laughter]
you know, part of the reason is because
of the war, you know, the USA
um USA has become the USA government
so-called deep state has been very
corrupt. So they are doing wars.
What? So what does it mean? Wars.
Killing people. That's basically what it
means. Okay. Killing people.
So imagine imagine the family.
Okay. I'm I'm kind of 60% drunk.
So imagine a family you know you you
just you know do nothing just you know
mind your own bi business business but
they kill you.
So that's u
that is what USA is doing. You know I I
I'm afraid
to post some some politics sometimes but
I see them.
Um [snorts]
anyway,
so so this that and uh
[sighs]
Okay, more drink.
Toilet paper. The most efficient
sanitary device.
[snorts]
Okay. So, but I wanted to tell you,
let's get back to technology. Okay. So,
but I wanted to tell you some of the
things I done for JavaScript and
cascading
stylesheet in the past month. Okay. So,
this is uh what is this? Cuz programming
blog archive 2026. Close it. What is
this? Casar programming blog archive
index. Okay.
Close.
What is this? Kasar blogging programming
blog. Okay. Uh, close it. Okay. Now,
Emacs blog. Close it. Okay. What I
wanted to tell you is um CSS blog. Okay.
So, show this page talk show. That's
right. Go to it. Show this page. Talk
show episode 86
today. Okay. Now go to CS. Um wait uh
this is what is this? Cuz JS TypeScript
what?
Uh JavaScript.
Um close that. What? Um
so go to C uh JavaScript. Okay. Copy the
file path show in browser kasa webde
blog. Okay. That's what I want to uh
show you guys. Okay.
Copy the file path. Close it. Show this
page in browser. Go here.
And uh make a new section. Paste the
link. Linkify it. And remove the to-do
and date showing browser. There it is.
Cuz web dev
webdev blog. Okay. So, I've been so busy
in the past um week on JavaScript stuff.
So, I finally created a tutorial for
weak JavaScript week map. Okay, that's
very interesting.
Uh, okay. Drink.
Okay. So I've done you know I I worked a
lot tremendously on this um
on these JavaScript issues weak map. So
there's a tutorial
uh is and so this is my tutorial but
it's kind of useless because today you
can ask AI you know you can ask AI to
you know AI write me a tutorial for
JavaScript weak map or tell me how
JavaScript weak map works it'll tell you
you know right away. So my tutorial is
kind of um
entirely useless in some way because
because of AI. Okay. But so I've been
asking AI, you know. So is it true that
AI has killed the entire tutorial
industry?
So I asked that question um like
yesterday or so somewhere here. Okay. So
but the yet the AI says not exactly in
fact many of the some some of the
tutorial industry is is still uh
prosperous. Okay.
[snorts]
like the big corporation um tutorial
industry. But anyway,
but I think uh but but I think
I think they are dead. Okay, because AI
really truly technically speaking AI
truly killed any tutorial industry or
textbooks
because AI can just generate answers and
correct answers, okay, right away. any
questions you have. So the tutorial
industry um
they might still be alive
mostly you know if they are still you
know I would say due to like social um
like they are trying to keep it alive
artificially like due to corporations
and so on but but but
from a user point of view like there's
no reason for uh any of the tutorial to
exist because AI can just answer it you
know correct answers any questions you
have about any technology sciences or
any you know calculus or math or
anything. Okay. Anyway, so I I I but
anyway so my um my tutorial is now today
is kind of like just notes my for
myself. Okay, it's kind of still useful
if you prefer um to read
things written by human. Okay, so there
it is. Uh JavaScript weak map.
Um and but also JavaScript, you know,
you see there's a mosa. So most of you
probably know
if you search any question about
JavaScript
the first result on web search is
Mosilla this MDN you know the from the
Firefox organization right so they
basically they became the number one uh
source for everything every for anything
JavaScript
So,
so you have two options. One is AI
answer. Okay. The other one is Mozilla,
you know, it's open source. It's it's
actually like um you know open source
documentation. For example, you can
check their license. You can copy and
paste if you want.
[snorts]
community participation
guidelines, legal telemetry settings.
You know, Mozilla, [ __ ] Mozilla is
actually uh kind of deep state, part of
the deep state. Okay. And you got
portions of this content are copyright
1998 to 2026
by individual mosina.org contributors.
Okay. [snorts] and content available
under a creative common license
which basically means anyone can copy
you know all you have to do is that you
know this you know my work is originally
from
Mosa okay that's all you have to say
so anyway so you got this Mosilla uh
reference
which beginning about 10 years ago they
Uh
they were promoted by deep state. Okay.
Anyway, uh so what what am I going
anyway? So
so what I'm saying is that today if you
want to know anything about JavaScript,
you have two major choices. One is just
ask AI. AI just you know going to answer
your question
uh on the spot. The other solution the
other uh source is Mozilla. Okay.
Anyway, so of course I still uh try you
know maintain my own tutorial JavaScript
in depth
god what am I doing? Uh I don't know. So
anyway, so I started to I um
in past week I worked a lot on
JavaScript.
So you got week we week map. So So what
what what is the point of about my
website tutorial?
Well, the point is that my version is
more focused on
a mathematical orientation. Okay.
[sighs]
Uh okay. So that's that. Uh yeah.
So and and also uh interesting is that
in 2026 you have this new method in
JavaScript called for the map object
called get get or insert which is
frequently used like um
okay
okay I think I'm drunk okay I'm 50% 60%
drunk And that [laughter]
that's it for today.
So what you guys saying? So I can't
paste links. That's right. Because of
the YouTube the way things are. Thoughts
on Destiny. Uh the streamer Destiny.
Okay. That guy is a [ __ ] Okay. That
guy is like
the streamer Destiny. That that guy is a
deep state
extreme [ __ ] Okay.
He's pretty smart. Okay. Because you
can't be a idiot
and be hired by deep state.
So the destiny guy um we are talking
about politics. The the destiny guy is a
extreme
you know he's basically a paid agent.
He's uh someone who got paid by the deep
state to influence your thought. Okay.
Destiny.
So on on one hand, he's super
intelligent. Okay. He's high IQ, you
know, because he
you you you you
have to I think you have to some
somewhat you have to be a successful.
You have to be high IQ in order to be a
YouTube influencer. Okay.
on one hand.
So, Destiny is a smart guy. Okay. On the
other hand, he's he's kind of idiot.
Okay. He's kind of idiot. Um,
you know, he's intelligent, but he, you
know, he he's an agent. So, what can you
say? He's a you know, you you take money
like someone pays me and I say things.
Okay.
Um, that's, you know, that's what
Destiny is.
Okay. So, [laughter] and then you say,
uh, Destiny and Tom Scott are your
favorite. Okay.
Now, Tom Scott is a, um, more innocent.
Okay. So, I don't think Tom Scott is a
agent.
I don't think you know to so destiny is
destiny is a guy who talk about politics
at all times. Okay.
But Tom Scott is not Tom Scott is more
uh more kind of naive more kind of
natural
YouTuber
and very popular. Of course they they
they got millions uh followers
you know like far more than me. They are
very successful.
Tom Scott. Okay.
So Tom Scott I would say
he's um you know not you know he's just
average like he's more of a like know
me. Okay. So Tom Scott. So, here's my um
my characterization
and my view of Tom Scott. Tom Scott is a
YouTube influencer. Okay, you can see
he's got 6.7
million subscribers.
So, he's very successful.
You know, if you have 6 million subs
subscribers, that also means you are a
millionaire. you are pretty rich. Okay,
very successful and rich.
But to me, he's uh Tom Scott is uh kind
of a know me. So he's just uh
you know, he he's just
follow the rules and make money. Okay,
that's why
That's
so basically that's what I think of him.
Okay, that's that's that's all.
Meanwhile, the Destiny guy is very uh
corrupt. Okay, Destiny.
Okay, this you know his name um let's
see
Destiny influencer his name
you know he he his name is Stephen uh
Kenneth Bonell a very corrupt guy a
scumbag. Okay.
So, let's see. Uh, so let me show you
the his uh video. Okay. This this guy,
okay, you know, very um
basically he's a deep state agent. Okay.
Uh let's see. Let's see his homepage.
And he's very smart. Okay. Very smart
guy.
[snorts] Uh these days, okay, here
that's his homepage.
Uh very smart guy,
but uh deep state agent and they make a
lot of money. They are more, you know,
they are more than
millions. They are more than
millionaires.
Okay.
So, you see I got now 10 concurrent
viewers. Okay. Bye, guys. That's it for
today.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm kind of uh drunk. So,
bye guys. I'm going to go enjoy noodles.